机舱乘务员 准备着陆 谢谢
Cabin crew, prepare for landing, thank you.
欢迎来到曼谷 希望您在这里享受一下
Welcome to Bangkok, we hope you enjoy your stay.
谢谢
Mahalo.
下一个
Next.
下一站 拉查普拉罗普站
Next station, Ratchaprarop Station.
晚上好 先生 我希望我没有让你等太久
Good evening, sir. I hope I didn't make you wait for too long.
哦 一点也没有 你很准时 非常完美
Oh, not at all, you're right on time. Perfect, actually.
我希望你睡个好觉
I hope you had a nice nap.
-水
- Water.
-谢谢 -欢迎你
- Thank you - You're welcome.
你不是在开玩笑吧
You weren't kidding about the traffic.
信不信由你 我预期的更糟
Believe it or not, I was expecting much worse.
我们现在不太远了
We're not too far away now.
呃...嗯
Uh... Ahem.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦 谢谢
Oh... Thank you.
大多数人只是把它扔到一边
Most people would just toss it to the side.
大多数人是轻率的
Most people are inconsiderate.
这辆车一尘不染
This car is spotless.
你一定很喜欢这份工作
You must really like this job.
嗯 这钱赚的很体面
Well, it's decent money.
另外 我的时间很自由
Plus, I get to choose my own hours,
我遇到很多有趣的人
and I get to meet a lot of interesting people.
你喜欢晚上开车吗？
You like to drive at night?
我晚上有更多的时间
I have more time at night.
不会变得危险吗？
Can't it get dangerous?
可能吧 但我很幸运
Probably, but I've been lucky.
此外 应用程序会告诉我
Plus, the app tells me where I'm being called
我要去哪里 一切都可以
and where I'm heading to so, it's all right.
你是个非常漂亮的女人
You're a very pretty woman.
你总是被人挑逗
You must get propositioned all the time.
如果他们停下来 我会担心的
I'll be worried if they stop.
我不再年轻了 你知道的
I'm not getting any younger, you know.
我想你没结婚？
I take it you're not married?
-不 -我能问你...为什么？
- No. - May I ask you... why?
从来没有绕过它
Never got around to it.
我有一个哥哥 他有个女人
I have a brother, he has MS.
他们十年前就发现了
They detected it ten years ago.
他现在25岁
He's 25 now.
他对我来说就是一切
He's everything to me.
我肯定他是
I'm sure he is.
我相信你正在尽你所能及
And I'm sure you're doing everything you can.
没错
I am.
只是过去的一年...
It's just this past year...
情况变得更糟了
It's gotten much worse.
是的
Yeah.
女人都这样
MS can be like that.
很多人因此而痛苦
A lot of people who suffer from it
往往比他们期望的要长得多
tend to live a lot longer than they're expected to.
你是医生吗？
Are you a doctor?
不
No.
但我很久以前还是一名野战医生
But I was a field medic a long time ago.
我对很多事情都了解一点
I know a little about a lot of things.
万事通 是吧？
Jack of all trades, huh?
毫无疑问 没错
Master of none, that's right.
-你的英语很好 -谢谢
- Your English is very good. - Well, thank you.
我在大学里学过英语 那是很久以前的事了
I studied English in college, and that was a long time ago.
我不会谈论你的年龄
Well, I won't talk about your age
如果你不谈论我的白胡子
if you don't talk about my white beard.
我也看很多电影 还有Youtube视频
I watch a lot of movies as well, also YouTube videos.
我就是这样练习英语的
That's how I practice my English,
但我仍然觉得我的词汇还不够
but I still feel like my vocabulary isn't there yet.
你听起来很棒
Well, you sound great to me.
尽管你是泰国人
Besides you're Thai,
你不需要说完美的英语
you don't need to speak perfect English.
其实我是一半英语是和我爸爸学的
I'm actually half, my dad's English.
但我在这里长大 一直住在这里
But I grew up here and lived here all my life.
谁知道呢 你知道 也许有一天我会
Who knows, you know, maybe one day I'm going to be
生活在一个只说英语 没有泰语的国家
living in a country where they only speak English, and no more Thai.
嗯 办公楼就在前面
Well, the office building is just up ahead.
你能把车停在前面吗？
Can you pull up in the front?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hm.
好了 我们来了
All right, we're here.
我叫凯
My name is Kai.
在夏威夷语中 它的意思是"大海"
In Hawaiian it means "the sea."
哦 太美了 你是夏威夷人？
Oh, that's very beautiful. You're from Hawaii?
是的
Yes.
我叫法
My name is Fha.
在泰语中的意思是"天空"
It means "sky" in Thai.
我很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你 法
Nice to meet you, Fha.
今晚生意怎么样？
How's business been tonight?
你是我的第一个客户我刚开始轮班
You're my first customer. I just started my shift.
-如果你不介意我问... -嗯？
- If you don't mind me asking... - Mm-hm?
你周五晚上平均赚多少钱？
How much do you make on an average Friday night?
我想是1500泰铢 如果天气好的话是2000泰铢
I would say 1,500 baht, and 2,000 on a good night.
六十美元？
Sixty dollars?
是的 我想是的 是的
Yeah, I think so, yes.
我有一个报价给你
I have an offer for you.
如果你决定接受它 你将不得不关闭应用程序
If you decide to take it you'll have to turn off the app.
好
Okay.
在这之后 我还有四站 都在城市
I have four more stops after this one, all in the city.
一千美元 那是定金
One-thousand dollars, that's the deposit.
你可以随时退出 拿钱
You can quit anytime, take the money.
但如果你决定陪我到最后
But if you decide to stay with me until the end,
我给你5000美元现金
I'll give you $5,000 in cash.
你不必做任何事情
You don't have to do anything.
你甚至不必下车 除非你想
You don't even have to get out of the car unless you want to.
我只是需要你帮我开车
I just need you to drive for me.
我需要去和律师谈谈 在这儿等我
I need to go up to talk with a lawyer. Wait for me here.
当我回来的时候 我会回答你可能有的任何问题
When I get back, I'll answer any questions you may have.
好吧？
All right?
谢谢
Thank you.
最后谢谢我
Thank me at the end.
你好
Hello.
四十三楼
Forty-third floor.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
-晚上好 卡哈勒先生 -晚上好
- Good evening, Mr. Kahale. - Good evening.
-你的航班怎么样？ -速度很快
- How was your flight? - It was quick.
那很好
That's nice.
坤查查其实在等你
Khun Cha Cha is actually waiting for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
欢迎来到曼谷 卡哈勒先生
Welcome to Bangkok, Mr. Kahale.
非常感谢 坤查查
Thank you so much, Khun Cha Cha.
很抱歉让你久等
Sorry to keep you waiting.
没事的 请坐一坐
Not at all. Please, have a seat.
谢谢
Thank you.
你有一个漂亮的办公室
You have a beautiful office.
看来你做得很好
Seems like you've done quite well,
尤其是这么年轻
especially for being so young.
是的 是这样
Yes, I have.
所以 请告诉我 我怎样才能提供服务？
So, please, tell me. How I can be of service?
你在电话里有点含糊不清
You were a bit vague on the phone,
关于事故和家庭成员的事情
something about an accident and a family member.
是的
Yes.
实际上 不止一个家庭成员
Actually, more than just one family member,
全家人
the whole family.
让我给你看点东西
Let me show you something.
谢谢你 坤查查明天见
Thank you, Khun Cha Cha. I'll see you tomorrow.
再次感谢您的等待
Thank you again for waiting.
小意思 一切都还好吧？
Not a problem at all. Did everything go okay?
-很好 -很好
- Very well. - Good.
我明天下午4点左右回来
I'll be back tomorrow around 4:00 pm
跟进详细信息
to follow up with details.
好吧
All right.
请你帮我个忙好吗？
Would you please do me a small favor?
当然
Of course.
有点不寻常
It's a bit unusual.
呃 你能叫辆出租车吗？
Uh, can you please ask for a taxi,
具体来说 一个粉红色的？
and specifically, a pink one?
我知道这很傻
I know it's silly.
但我在机场看到很多粉红色的出租车
But I saw a lot of the pink taxis at the airport,
我的旅行中一辆这样的车都还没坐过
and with all my travels I've never ridden in one.
-当然 是的 -好的 谢谢
- Sure, yeah. - Okay, thank you.
现在 请让他们知道会有两站
Now, please let them know there'll be two stops:
一个在24小时超市
one at a 24-hour supermarket,
然后在我的酒店 千禧酒店
and then at my hotel, the Hotel Millennium.
好吧 这一点也不问题
Okay, that's not a problem at all.
大概需要十分钟
It'll take maybe about ten minutes.
你介意在这里等吗？或者
Would you mind waiting here? Or...
嗯 实际上 我更喜欢在外面等
Uh, actually, I prefer waiting outside.
-好的 -嗯 我想我的身体
- Okay. - Um, I think my body
可以呼吸新鲜的非空调空气
could use some fresh non-airconditioned air.
-是的 好吧 很棒 -再次感谢你
- Yeah, okay. Great. - Thank you again.
祝你晚上愉快
Have a good evening.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦 天哪 你吓到我了
Oh, my gosh, you scared me.
对不起 你应该锁门
Sorry, you should lock the doors.
一切都很顺利？
Everything went well?
律师非常配合
The lawyer was very cooperative.
我不喜欢律师
Well, I don't like lawyers.
没关系 我也不知道
It's okay, I don't either.
那么 接下来呢？
So, where next?
通勒警察局 请
Thonglor Police Station, please.
我知道 先是律师 现在是警察
I know, first a lawyer, now police.
嗯 你有麻烦吗？
Mm-hm. Are you in trouble?
不 不是这样的
No, it's nothing like that.
律师和警察
The lawyer and the police officer
最近我女儿和她的家人正在审理一个案件
were working on a case that involved my daughter and her family recently.
我是来报答他们的
I'm here to repay them.
我们将在晚上11点左右到达那里
We're gonna get there around 11:00 pm.
那你能看见他们吗？
Will you be able to see them then?
我相信这不会是个问题
I'm sure that won't be a problem.
伙计 你很容易睡着
Man, you fall asleep so easily.
每辆行驶中的车辆
Every moving vehicle.
我发现我喜欢这个动作
I find I like the motion.
你喜欢做什么？
What do you like to do?
当你不是...
When you're not...
开车还是照顾你哥哥？
driving or taking care of your brother?
我不知道
I don't know.
我真的没有太多的时间
I don't really have much time
做任何事情
to do anything else.
你一定喜欢某样东西
You must like something.
那你呢？
Well, what about you?
钓鱼 我喜欢钓鱼
Fishing. I like fishing.
-钓鱼？-钓鱼
- Fishing? - Fishing.
钓鱼听起来太无聊了
Fishing sounds so boring.
你试过吗？
Have you tried it?
没有 但我知道它是什么 它看起来很无聊
No, but I know what it is, and it looks boring.
鱼就像人
Fish are like people.
喜欢人吗？
Like people?
就像人一样
Like people.
如何？
How?
嗯 有一些鱼
Well, there are some fish
那是...真的很笨 很容易抓住
that are... really dumb and easy to catch.
其他人非常聪明
Others are extremely smart
很难抓住
and much more difficult to catch.
然后是罕见的 危险的...
And then there are the rare, dangerous ones...
会伤害你 甚至杀人
that can hurt or even kill you.
我真的觉得很放松...钓鱼的行为
I actually find it relaxing... the act of fishing.
我不在乎我是否抓到一条鱼
I don't really care whether I catch a fish or not.
我只是喜欢站在海滩上...
I just like standing on a beach...
看着海浪滚滚而来...
watching the waves roll in...
听他们在沙滩上崩溃...
listening to them crash on the sand...
感受我脸上的暖风...
feeling the warm breeze on my face...
闻到盐的味道...
smelling the salt...
和空气中的花香
and the scent of flowers in the air.
我就是这样钓鱼的
That's how I fish.
这就是我祖父教我的
That's what my grandfather taught me.
这就是我喜欢的
That's what I like.
对我来说 这是天堂
It's heaven to me.
听起来很平静
It sounds very peaceful.
你应该试试
You should try it.
也许有一天
Maybe one day.
我们到了
We're here.
你要我把车停在前面吗？
Do you want me to park in front?
是的 把车停在前面
Yeah, park in front.
好
Okay.
我马上就回来
I'll be back soon.
搞什么？
What the fuck?
我知道你会说英语
I know you speak English.
这是为丽莎准备的
This is for Lisa.
到底是谁...
Who the fuck is...
你还在这里
You're still here.
老实说 我想离开
To be honest, I thought about leaving.
你看到我把包忘了
You saw I left the bag.
你打开了吗？
Did you open it?
但你知道里面有现金吗？
But you know there's cash inside?
是测试吗？
Was it a test?
哦 我的上帝！你的头怎么了？
Oh, my God! What happened to your head?
我绊倒 撞墙了
I tripped. Hit the wall.
你需要缝针 也许三到四针
You need stitches, maybe three or four.
不 我很好谢谢
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
是否确定？那是很深的伤口
Are you sure? That's a deep cut.
我确定
I'm sure.
好吧
All right.
呼吸
Breathe.
不 这不是一个测试
And, no, it wasn't a test.
生活中一切都是为了做出选择
Everything in life is about making choices.
我选择离开包
I chose to leave the bag.
你选择不拿它
You chose not to take it.
生活就是做出选择
Life is about making choices
并处理这些后果
and dealing with those consequences.
你明白吗？
You understand that?
我理解
I understand.
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
我们来吃点东西吧
Let's get something to eat.
我们有时间
We have some time.
你想吃什么？
What do you feel like eating?
当地的东西
Something local.
嗯 我只知道那个地方
Well, I know just the place.
好
Okay.
我是说 来吧 宝贝
I mean, come on, babe,
谁在星期五晚上杀了律师？
who fucking kills a lawyer on a Friday night?
停下！你在现场？
Stop it! You're on the scene?
其实我现在只是走了进去
I'm actually just walking in now.
凯·卡哈勒 美国夏威夷人
Kai Kahale, American-Hawaiian.
今天刚到 他直接来了
Just arrived today, he came straight here.
他有个约会
He had an appointment.
她领着他到死者的办公室
She led him to the vic's office,
接下来你知道他要求打车
next thing you know he asks for a taxi,
她发现她的老板被枪杀了 一颗子弹射到头部
she finds her boss shot dead. Boom, a bullet to the head.
他走了出去 好像什么都没发生
He walked out of here as if it was nothing.
卫兵也证实了这一点
Guards confirmed it as well.
就像我说的 冷血的
Like I said, cold-blooded.
身体倒了下去
Body slumped over.
血在她身后到处乱溅
Blood splattered everywhere directly behind her.
这个凯·卡哈勒坐在她面前 朝她开了一枪
This Kai Kahale sat directly in front of her and shot her.
我在看他的身份证
I'm looking at his ID.
看起来是真的
Seems to be real.
今晚5点从羽田到达
Arrived this evening, 5:00 pm, from Haneda.
TG614 商务舱
TG 614, business class.
转机
Connecting flight.
没有别名？
No alias?
凯·卡哈勒 1954年出生 退休
Kai Kahale, born 1954. Retired.
在咖啡种植园当过主管 看起来是个大块头
Worked as a supervisor at a coffee plantation, big one it seems.
他用消音器朝她开了一枪
He shot her with a silencer, one shot.
他绝对不是办公室工作人员
He's definitely not an office worker.
把照片拿出来 把它送到机场和边境
Get his picture out. Send it out to the airports and the borders.
谁知道呢 也许我们会很幸运
Who knows, maybe we'll get lucky.
好的 尽可能多地获取信息
All right, get as much information as you can
送我去办公室 我把车开在那儿了
and drop me off at the office. I left my car there.
叔叔 请两个普通的
Uncle, two of the usual, please.
确定
Sure.
你想喝点什么？
What would you like to drink?
呃...？
Uh...?
我建议你喝菊花茶
I'd recommend you the chrysanthemum tea.
真的令人耳目一新 是的？
It's really refreshing. Yeah?
-太完美了 -太完美了
- Perfect. - Perfect.
叔叔 请两个菊花茶
Uncle, two chrysanthemum tea, please.
继续
Go ahead.
-谢谢 -顾客还是男朋友？
- Thank you. - Customer or boyfriend?
-他是顾客 -那很好
- He's a customer. - That's good.
因为他看起来比你爸爸还大
Because he looks even older than your dad.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
你是这里的常客？
You're a regular here?
是的 我试着来这里
Yeah, I try to come here
每周两三次 取决于我的车
two or three times a week, depends on my ride.
好？
Good?
好
Good.
我现在能问你个问题吗？
Can I ask you a question now?
什么
Anything.
六千美元是一大笔钱
Six-thousand dollars is a lot of money,
谁都愿意花一半甚至更少的钱去做
and anyone would do it for half or even less.
可能
Probably.
但为什么是6000？
But why 6,000?
因为我想让你答应
Because I wanted you to say yes.
我想要你
And I wanted you
想做 并快乐地做
to want to do it and be happy doing it.
好
Okay...
但说实话 我只能拿一半
But to be honest, I can just take half,
对我来说已经足够了
it's more than enough for me.
不 我们做了个交易
No, we made a deal,
我们摇了摇它
we shook on it.
是否确定？
Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
好 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
正如我说的 谢谢我之后
As I said, thank me after.
什么之后？
After what?
哦 不 不 等等
Oh, no, no, wait.
你需要先把这个放进去
You need to put some of this in first.
一些坚果
Some nuts.
一些 我不知道你用英语怎么称呼这个
Some... I don't know what you call this in English.
但它会让它尝起来很美味
But it will make it taste good.
你吃辣椒吗？
Do you eat chili?
我愿意
I do.
谢谢
Thank you.
然后你需要这个
And then you need this,
这就像秘方
this is like the secret recipe.
-鱼酱 -鱼酱？
- Fish sauce. - Fish sauce?
好了 钻进去
Okay, done, dig in.
祝你胃口好
Bon appétit.
-胃口好 -梅西
- Bon appétit. - Merci.
嗯 味道很好
Mmm, smells so good.
很好 对吧？
It's good, right?
真的很不错
It's really good.
真棒
Great.
那么 这之后是什么？
So, what's after this?
之后
After.
我们在俱乐部停留
We have a stop at a club.
-嗯 -然后我们去医院
- Mm-hm. - Then we go to a hospital.
最后一站是一所房子
And the last stop is at a house.
你今天要见五个人？
You're meeting five people today?
不 七个
No, seven.
你想知道为什么
And you want to know why.
是的 对不起
Yeah, sorry.
没事 人的本性
It's okay, human nature.
不久前...
Not too long ago...
我女儿和她的家人来到了泰国
my daughter and her family came to Thailand.
他们出事了
They got into an accident.
今晚我要见的人
The people I'll be seeing tonight
参与了这件事
were involved with it.
明白了
I see.
他们没事吧？
Are they okay?
不
No.
他们死了
They died.
哦
Oh.
我...对不起
I'm... I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
我最近也出事了
I was recently in an accident as well.
白人家庭...
White family...
他们也死了
They died too.
醉酒司机
Drunk driver.
世界各地都发生了
Happens everywhere in the world.
他们有个孩子
They have a kid.
一个孩子
A child.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢你带我来这里并支付晚餐
Thank you for bringing me here and for paying for dinner.
-太棒了 -欢迎你
- It was excellent. - You're welcome.
而且 嗯 我很抱歉 没有这么高兴的谈话
And, uh, I'm sorry about the not so happy conversation.
没事 这就是生活
It's okay, it's life.
呃...
Uh...
你知道伊维萨夜总会吗？
Do you know the Ibiza night club?
是的 那是我们的下一个目的地吗？
Yeah. Is that our next destination?
-是的 -好的
- Yes. - Okay.
十字架 你不是佛教徒？
A cross, you're not Buddhist?
不
No.
我也不是基督徒
I'm not Christian either.
你是无神论者吗？
Are you atheist?
什么是无神论者？
What's atheist?
无神论者是一个不相信宗教的人
Atheist is someone who does not believe in religion.
我相信信仰
I believe in faith.
我相信人们有信仰是件好事
I believe it's good that people have faith.
你祈祷吗？
Do you pray?
是的
Yeah.
我能问谁吗？
May I ask to whom?
给我的父母
To my parents.
那为什么是十字架？
So why the cross?
它属于我认识的人
It belonged to someone I knew.
我留着它 作为提醒
I kept it as a reminder.
好的还是坏的提醒？
Good or bad reminder?
好的
Good.
我做了坏事
Of something bad I did.
你做了坏事？
You did something bad?
是的
Yeah.
有人受伤吗？
Did anyone get hurt?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
但你感觉不好
But you feel bad.
我觉得...
Yeah, I feel...
我 我不知道该怎么解释
I... I don't know how to explain.
内疚
Guilt.
你感到内疚
You feel guilty.
内疚是好的
Guilt is good.
它提醒着我们做好
It reminds us to do good.
这就是我留着十字架的原因
That's why I kept the cross.
开车四处走走 靠近
Drive around. Stay close.
我会打电话的 别接电话
I'll call, don't pick up the phone.
在那边见我 经过入口
Meet me over there, past the entrance,
在五分钟内打电话
within five minutes of the phone call.
好
Okay.
妈的 伙计？
What the fuck, man?
-多米尼克！- 妈的！
- Dominic! - Holy fuck!
你搞砸了 呆在原地
You messed up. Stay put.
什么...你...你想要什么？
What... What do you... What do you want?
你用保时捷杀了一家人 你还记得吗？
You killed a family with your Porsche, do you remember?
你还记得吗？！
Do you remember?!
是的 是的 是的...我 我记得
Yes, yes, yes, yes... I... I remember.
只是不要...不要 什么都不做
Just don't... don't... don't do anything.
站起来
Stand up.
等等 不 别...别杀人...
Wait, no, don't... Just don't kill...
上帝啊！
Jesus Christ!
-站起来！-好的...我什么都没做！
- Stand up! - Okay... I didn't do anything!
你想要吗 你想要我的车吗？
Do you want... Do you want my car?
拿吧 伙计 这是你的
Take it, man, it's yours.
-发生什么事了？-开车
- What happened? - Drive.
-你做了什么？-请开车
- What did you do? - Drive, please.
最近的医院在哪里？
Where's the nearest hospital?
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
我没事 医院
I'm okay, hospital.
还有几分钟的路程
There's one a few minutes away.
请带我们去那里
Take us there, please.
请！
Please!
你在想什么？
What are you thinking?
我想还有更多
I'm thinking there's more.
我想它会升级
I'm thinking that it's going to escalate.
我想他不是睡在旅馆里
And I'm thinking he's not sleeping in a hotel somewhere.
我们需要把一切都放在这三个人身上
We need to get everything on these three people.
妻子在上面 她很快就会有东西给我们了
Wife's on it. She should have something for us soon.
你儿子不是一个星期大吗？
Isn't your son like a week old?
-九天 -说曹操曹操到
- Nine days. - Talk about a slave driver.
你见过我妻子 对吧？
You met my wife, right?
你知道她不休息
You know she doesn't rest.
说
Speak.
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks.
好像你又对了
Seems like you're right again.
-在哪儿？ -伊维萨夜总会
- Where? - Ibiza Night Club.
二十三岁 胸部中弹
Twenty-three-year-old, shot through the chest.
-目击所有索赔...老亚洲男子 -好的
- Witness all claim... old Asian man. - All right.
等等 老板 还有那孩子 他没死
Wait, boss, there's more. The kid, he's not dead.
我们说话时 他正被送往医院
He's being transported to the hospital as we speak.
你去俱乐部 确认身份 四处看看
You go to the club, get a positive ID, take a look around,
我会去医院
and I'll head over to the hospital.
收到
Copy that.
能给我纸巾吗？
Can I have a tissue, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我不会杀了你
I'm not going to kill you.
一切都没有改变
Nothing has changed.
我们的交易仍然是交易
Our deal is still the deal.
这不是意外 对吧 我今晚来接你？
It wasn't an accident, right, me picking you up tonight?
不 不是
No, it wasn't.
我知道你住在哪里
I know where you live.
我知道你的例行公事
I knew your routine.
为什么？
Why?
死在你车里的家人...
The family that died in your car...
那是我女儿...
that was my daughter...
她丈夫...
her husband...
还有她五岁的女儿
and her five-year-old daughter.
我的孙子
My grandchild.
你要杀了我？
You gonna kill me?
这是可能的...是的
It was possible... yes.
是你的车 你证人证上的签名
It was your car, your signature on the witness sheet.
我发誓 我不想杀你
I swear, I don't want to kill you.
我甚至不想伤害你
I don't even want to hurt you.
你能给我一瓶水吗？
Can you give me a bottle of water, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
喝吧
Drink it.
是什么改变了你的想法？
What changed your mind?
那个
That.
我把它给了我女儿...
I gave that to my daughter...
在她18岁生日的时候
on her 18th birthday.
任何能忍受你一样多的内疚的人...
Anyone who can live with as much guilt as you do...
在做出选择时...
over making a choice...
你别无选择
You had no option.
那个人有一颗善良的心
That person has a good heart.
你要杀了他？
You're going to kill him?
是的
Yes.
这是什么地方？
What kind of fucking place is this?
-这是你吗？-你什么意思？
- Is this you? - What the fuck do you mean?
这是你的生意伙伴吗？
Is this one of your business associates?
你有某种交易不好吗？
Did you have some sort of deal go bad?
操你妈！
Fuck you!
操你妈的 你居然这么想
Fuck you for even thinking that.
我怎么能不想呢？
How can I not think it?
你把我们置于危险之中多少次了？
How many times have you put us in danger?
-真的吗？ -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
你中枪多少次了？
How many times have you been shot at?
多姆有多少次了？
How many times has Dom?
没错 没有
That's right, none.
我从来没有把我们置于危险之中
I have never put us in danger.
我给你的生活
The life I provide you with,
百分之九十九的会为之杀人
ninety-nine percent of the population would kill for.
所以 我非常感激大家的尊重！
So, I would appreciate some respect!
事实上我让你操你的小娘儿们已经够尊重了
The fact that I let you fuck your little hussies is respect enough.
你以为我不知道吗？
What, you think I don't know?
你以为我是瞎子
You think I'm some farang who's blind
不知道怎么回事？
and doesn't know what's going on?
你什么也做不了
Nothing you do goes by me.
我可以带我儿子去
I can take my son
带着你所拥有的一切走开
and walk away with everything you got.
我知道你所有肮脏的小秘密
I know all your dirty little secrets.
所以我还站在这里
So the fact that I'm still standing here,
这就是你会得到的所有尊重
that's all the respect you're going to get.
如果我儿子死了...我向上帝发誓
And if my son dies... I swear to God,
你会后悔你曾经盯着我的那一天
you'll regret the day that you ever laid eyes on me.
他是个幸运的男孩
He's a lucky boy.
子弹擦干净了
The bullet went clean through.
他们只有清理他的伤口 并缝合他
All they had to do was clean his wounds and stitch him up.
他会没事的
He's gonna be okay.
你被解雇了 没用的屎！
You're fired... useless piece of shit!
你朝我儿子开枪了？！
You fucking shot my son?!
等等！这到底是干什么用的？
Wait, wait, wait! What is this all about?
听着 任何你想要的 我有这么多钱
Listen, anything you want. I have so much money.
你的钱都付了
Your money paid for everything.
让我的儿媳变成罪犯
Made my son-in-law into a criminal.
你掩盖了你儿子的罪行！
You covered your son's crimes!
是的 你现在明白了
Yeah, you understand now.
我这样做是为了保护我的儿子
I did it to protect my son.
任何父亲都会做的事
Something any father would do.
我也是
Me too.
苹果从不从树上掉下来
The apple never falls far from the tree.
他只是个孩子
He's just a kid.
你够大了 可以杀人了...你足够大了 可以死了
You're old enough to kill... you're old enough to die
你说什么了？
Well, what do you got?
胸部受伤
Hurt boobies.
像爸爸 像儿子
Like father, like son.
我发现警察和律师在20多起案件中有联系
I found connections between the cops and the lawyers in over 20 cases.
从小交通违章到更严重的犯罪
From small traffic violations to more serious crimes.
例子？
Example?
毒品和人口贩运 私藏
Drug and human trafficking, possession.
你命名它 他们一起工作
You name it, they worked on it together.
被告走的每一个实例
And for every instance the defendants walked.
不过 只有一个案件涉及戴维斯家族
There was only one case involving the Davis family though.
-好的 -几个月前 儿子出事了
- Okay. - A few months ago, the son was involved in an accident.
四人死亡 一人受伤
Four people died and one was injured,
包括一个五岁的女孩 一个英国家庭
including a five-year-old girl. A British family.
-不是美国人？ -不 英国人
- Not American? - No, British.
-库珀一家 -儿子被判无罪
- The Coopers. - And the son got acquitted.
原来老公是开出租车的
Turns out the husband was the one driving the taxi.
付司机额外的钱 说他一直想在曼谷开车
Paid the driver extra, said he always wanted to drive in Bangkok.
弄糊涂了 开着车直奔前方的车流
Got confused, drove right onto coming traffic.
直接跑进儿子家
And ran directly into the son.
是的 那是官方版本
Yeah, that's the official version.
不 多亏了我们两个死去的朋友 我肯定
No, thanks to our two dead friends, I'm sure.
没错
Right.
你的想法？
Your thoughts?
我的想法是一样的 法律就是法律
My thoughts are the same, the law is the law.
警惕正义仍然是杀人
Vigilante justice is still homicide.
放下！
Drop it!
现在！
Now!
好了 伙计 放松点
Okay, man, relax.
我放下枪
I'm putting down the gun.
听着 我什么都知道
Look, I know everything.
儿子 他杀了你的家人 对吗？
The son, he killed your family, right?
儿子还是女儿？
Son or daughter?
我女儿
My daughter.
我明白 但没人再受伤了
I understand, but no one needs to get hurt anymore.
哦 是的 再一个人 那就完了
Oh, yes, one more person, then it's done.
唯一会受到伤害的人就是你
The only person that is gonna get hurt is you.
如果继续这样
If you continue this.
放下枪
Put down the gun.
来吧 伙计 让我们用正确的方法处理这件事
Come on, man, let's handle this the right way.
法律方法
The legal way.
是的 那不太顺利
Yeah, that didn't work out too well
为了我女儿和她的家人
for my daughter and her family.
那是我们 我道歉
And that's on us, and I apologize.
但到处都有好有坏
But there's good and bad everywhere.
-是的 -他们是坏人
- Yeah. - They were bad people
假装很好
pretending to be good.
你做不好
You are good doing bad,
两个错误不等于一个正确 伙计
and two wrongs don't make it right, man.
没有什么能做出正确的决定 甚至连这个都做不对
Nothing will make this right, not even this.
-那我们为什么要这么做？ -因为我可以
- So why are we doing this? - Because I can.
因为没有人这样做
Because no one else did.
不要
Don't.
我不想开枪打你
I don't want to shoot you,
我不想开枪打她 但我会的
I don't want to shoot her, but I will.
呆在那儿
Stay there.
走 走 走！
Go, go, go!
去
Go.
不！
No!
凯！
Kai!
不 妈的 呆在那儿！
No, fuckin' stay there!
凯 你不会开枪打我的
Kai, you're not gonna shoot me.
-我会开枪打你！ -让她走
- I will shoot you! - Let her go.
我不会让她走的 我不会让她走的！
I'm not letting her go. I'm not letting her go!
凯 请让她走 她什么也没做
Kai, please let her go, she didn't do anything.
-我不想伤害她！ -我没有枪
- I don't want to hurt her! - I don't have a gun.
凯 冷静点 你不是这样的
Kai, calm down. That's not you,
你不是那种人
you're not that type of man.
-他们已经死了 -呆在那儿！
- They're already dead. - Stay there!
凯 他们都死了 请让她走
Kai, they're all dead. Let her go, please.
-我求你了 -我要开枪打你
- I'm begging you. - I'm gonna shoot you.
我要开枪打你
I'm gonna shoot you.
我会开枪打你
I'll shoot you.
凯 让她走！
Kai, let her go!
你想开枪打我 然后开枪打我！
You want to shoot me, then shoot me!
但你现在让她走了！
But you fucking let her go now!
不是你 凯！
That's not you, Kai!
放开她！好？
Let her go! Okay?
我是父亲 就像你一样
I'm a father, just like you.
就像你一样 我是父亲 我明白
Just like you, I'm a father, I understand,
但请让她走吧
but please, just let her go. Please.
凯 听我说
Kai... Kai, listen to me.
放开她
Let her go.
不！
No!
这才是你！这才是你！
That's on you! That's on you!
不！
No!
救命！帮帮我！
Help! Help me!
警官下来！ 下来！
Officer down! Two down!
来吧 兄弟 呆在那儿 呆在那儿
Come on, bro, hang in there, hang in there.
我没有杀她 对吧？
I didn't kill her, right?
不 你没有 她很好 她会挺过来的
No, you didn't, she's good. She's going to make it. Okay.
他妈的！
Fuck!
他妈的
Fuck.
这是一个惊喜
This is a surprise.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我不知道
I don't know.
到处都是警察
There are cops everywhere.
是的 我明白
Yeah, I know.
没有按计划进行
Didn't go quite as well as planned.
把你的位置发给我
Send me your location.
他们不认识我的车 我离我很近
They don't know my car, I'm close.
我来接你
I'll come pick you up.
好吧
All right.
停在小巷里
Park in the alley.
你停车时我来看你
I'll see you when you pull up.
保持低调
Stay low.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们要去哪？
Where are we going?
你在流血 我们需要帮忙
You're bleeding, we need to fix you.
我很好
I'm fine.
子弹穿过了
Bullet went through.
-你怎么知道的？ -我感觉到了
- How do you know? - I felt it.
但我不能去医院
But I can't go to a hospital.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
侦探 他很好 他不会花很长时间
The detective, he's good. It won't take him long
在他弄清楚最后一个目标是谁之前
before he figure's out who the last target is.
最后一个目标 他自己...
And the last target himself...
他会知道接下来一个小时会发生什么...
He's gonna know what's going on in the next hour...
然后消失
and disappear.
我们不去医院 别担心
We're not going to the hospital, don't worry.
不太远
It's not too far away.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么样？
How are you holding up?
很好
Better.
你尽力了
You did your best.
我什么都听到了
I heard everything.
孩子29岁
Kid was 29.
他射杀了一名护士
He shot a nurse.
她24岁
She was 24.
他不是个孩子
He's not a kid.
还有另一个目标
There's another target.
我知道
I know.
这就是我来这里的原因
That's why I'm here.
你还记得那次事故吗？
You remember the accident?
有一人受伤
There was one person who was injured.
没死
Didn't die.
她叫瓦尼达·霍夫斯特德
Her name was Vanida Hoffsted.
她是个出租车司机
She was a cab driver.
在审判中作证的女孩
The girl that testified at the trial.
是的
Yeah.
今晚早些时候
Earlier tonight,
晚上8点左右 她从坚果路接人
she picked up someone from On Nut Road around 8:00 pm.
两小时后 把他丢在西洛姆路
Two hours later, dropped him off on Silom Road.
在律师事务所附近？
Near the law offices?
她现在在哪儿？
Well, where is she now?
在那之后 她关闭了她的应用程序
She turned her app off after that.
她驾驶着一辆新的沃尔沃 我有碟子
She was driving a new Volvo. I have the plates.
我们可以追踪她
We can track her.
如果她在路上 它很快就会出现
It'll show up if she's on the road.
-把所有东西都放上 -我已经订了
- Put everything on it. - I already ordered it.
当然了 宝贝
Of course you did, babe.
-你看到照片了 -停下
- You saw the photos. - Stop.
我知道你是一个善良的人...
I know you're a good-hearted person...
但他还是个冷血的杀人犯
but he's still a cold-blooded murderer.
他从来就不是
He never was one.
他曾在军队服役 40年前的两次旅行
He served in the military; two tours, 40 years ago.
从那以后 就没有一点瑕疵了
After that, not even a single blemish.
-甚至没有交通违章 -他还是个杀人犯
- Not even a traffic violation. - He's still a murderer.
他也是一位父亲
He's also a father.
就像你一样
Just like you.
你想说什么 我应该放弃一切？
What are you trying to say, I should just drop everything?
不 但我了解你
No, but I know you.
你刚刚看着你的年轻伴侣被枪杀
You just watched your young partner get shot and die.
你现在在意气用事
You're operating on emotions right now.
我只是来给你一些平衡
I'm just here to give you some balance.
你是个好人 和他一样
You're a good man, like him.
我不想看到你做坏事
I don't want to see you do a bad thing.
两个错误不等于一个正确
Two wrongs don't make a right.
我得去上班了
I gotta go work.
看看他
Look at him.
现在看着我
Now look at me.
你是个好警察 宝贝
You're a good cop, babe.
但请记住 你现在首先是父亲
But remember, you're a father now, first and foremost.
然后是丈夫 然后是警察
Then a husband, then a cop.
-我爱你 -迪托
- I love you. - Ditto.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
你有盐水或酒精吗？
Uh, do you have some saline or some alcohol
-先来哪个？-哦 对了 是的
- or something first? - Oh, right, yes.
哦 妈的
Oh, fuck.
-好的哦 谢谢 -对不起
- All right. Oh, thanks. - Sorry.
哦 天哪 那是很多血
Oh, my gosh, that's a lot of blood.
好
Okay...
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
好吧 这会伤到的
Okay, this is gonna hurt.
你为什么回来？
Why'd you come back?
对不起
Sorry.
我有机会纠正我所做的错误
I had a chance to correct the wrong that I did.
所以我做了一个选择
So I made a choice.
你说我们忍受着自己选择的后果
You said we live with the consequences of our own choice.
我之前做了一个坏的
I made a bad one before.
你别无选择
You didn't have a choice.
我现在知道了
I know that now.
哦 哦
Ow.
好
Okay.
他们给了我两百万泰铢...还有这辆车
They gave me two million baht... and this car.
他们让我说 我不是那个开车的人
They told me to say that I wasn't the one who was driving.
我们的车撞上了另一辆车
That our car hit the other car.
如果我不接受这个提议...
If I didn't take the offer...
我相信 他们可能会杀了我
I believe that they were probably going to kill me.
是的
Yes.
他们会的
They would have.
我把钱大部分花在了我哥哥身上
I spent most of my money on my brother.
提前支付了他的住院费用
Paid in advance for his hospital expenses.
现在剩下的不多了
There's not much left now.
好吧 转过去 你还有一个机会
Well, turn around, you've got one more to go.
哦
Ooh.
这样会伤得更重
This is gonna hurt more.
好吧 最后一个深呼吸
All right, last one. Take a deep breath.
谢谢
Thank you.
会留下一个大伤疤的
It's gonna leave a big scar.
没关系 这是很好的提醒
It's okay. It's a good reminder.
什么 今晚？
Of what, tonight?
你
Of you.
样样通 样样松
Jack of all trades.
其实我还有一个回来的理由
I actually have one more reason why I came back.
我两年前开始开车
I started driving two years ago.
在此之前 我曾经在酒店和餐馆工作
Before this, I used to work in hotels and restaurants.
我工作的地方 遇到过很多外国人
I meet a lot of foreigners everywhere I work.
所有的外国人 他们看到我 他们喜欢我
All the foreigners, they see me, they like me.
他们提供钱 让我和他们上床
They offered money for me to sleep with them.
但我从来不接受
But I'd never take it.
你明白？
You understand?
你是我遇到的第一个男人...在我的生命中
You're the first man that I've met... in my life
这显示了我的尊重
that showed me respect.
谁真正尊重我做的事
Who actually gave me respect for what I do.
我的工作
My work.
不是我长什么样
Not for what I look like.
这就是我回来的原因
That's why I came back.
这是自那以后任何人对我说的最好的事情...我老婆
That's the nicest thing anyone has said to me since... my wife.
这是事实
It's the truth.
会更好的
Makes it nicer.
呆在这儿
Stay here.
拿着这个
Hold this.
这个袋子里有4000美元现金
There's $4,000 cash in this bag.
是你的
It's yours.
你知道比特币吗？
Do you know Bitcoin?
比特...币
Bit... coin.
是的 我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
你知道是钱吗？
You know it's money?
就像电子货币一样
Like electronic money.
我在网上读到一些东西 但我不确定
I read something online, but I'm not sure.
好吧 不难发现
Okay, it's not hard to find out about.
包里是一个硬盘驱动器
Inside that bag is a hard drive.
我一生积蓄
My life savings.
一百三十八万九千美元
One-million, three-hundred and eighty-nine thousand dollars.
是你的
It's yours.
不 不 我不能接受这个
No, no, no, no, I cannot take this.
-不 听我说  -不 不 我不能
- No, no, no. Listen to me. - No, no, I cannot.
-听我说 听我说  -不
- Listen to me. Listen to me. - No.
我把它转换成比特币
I converted it to bitcoin.
我不知道还能做什么
I didn't know what else to do.
我在想 也许
Uh, I was thinking, maybe,
之后我可以捐给慈善机构
I could donate it to charity afterwards,
但对我来说 没有之后
but there is no afterwards for me.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
我是说 最后一个人和别人不一样
I mean, the last guy is different from the others.
他更危险
He's much more dangerous.
更聪明
Much smarter.
更会防守
Better guarded.
所以你认为你赢不了？
So you think you cannot win?
对我来说 这从来就不是胜利
It was never about winning for me.
即使我活下来了 我也会坐牢的
Even if I survive, I'll go to prison.
我应该去监狱
I should go to prison.
但我不能去那里 你明白吗？
But I can't go there, you understand?
我理解
I understand.
所以 你必须采取这个
So you must take this.
因为如果你接受这个 你会赢
Because if you take this, you win.
如果你赢了 我赢了
And if you win, I win.
你带走你哥哥 然后拿到护照
You take your brother and you get some passports.
你带他去一个不会说泰语的国家
And you take him to some country that doesn't speak Thai,
如果这是你真正想要的
if that's what you really want.
好吗？
Okay?
好
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
这个人是谁？
Who is this man?
他是日本人
He's Japanese.
-八九三黑帮？ -不
- Like Yakuza? - No.
但他和他们一起工作
But he works with them.
他和任何能付出代价的人一起工作
He works with anyone who can pay his price.
这是...非常高
Which is... very high.
做什么？
To do what?
解决问题
To solve problems.
比如？
Like?
比如 如果你杀了人
Like, if you kill someone
你需要摆脱尸体
and you need to get rid of the body.
如果你因为酒后驾车而被捕 杀死一个家庭...
If you get arrested for drunk driving, killing a family...
他可以解决
he can fix it.
那他真是个坏人
He's a really bad man then.
最糟糕的一个
One of the worst.
这类人可以做很多坏事
A type of person who can do a lot of bad things
却不会因此而弄脏自己
and not get dirty for it.
你似乎对他了解很多
Well, you seem to know a lot about him.
我雇了他
I hired him.
什么？
What?
他为我安排了一切
He arranged everything for me.
包 枪 电话 一切
The bag, the gun, the phone, everything.
哦 你真聪明 凯先生
Oh, well, you're really smart, Mr. Kai.
别走 做出选择
Don't go. Make a choice.
带我和我哥哥去夏威夷
Take me and my brother to Hawaii.
我们可以去钓鱼
We can go fishing.
那太好了
That would be nice.
你一起钓鱼...和你哥哥
Fishing with you... and your brother.
祝你好运
Good luck...
坤法
Khun Fha.
嘿！
Hey!
嘿 你这个混蛋！
Hey, you motherfucker!
你们让这些人都在为你而战
You got all these guys fighting for you,
你不能自己做吗？
you can't do it yourself?
嗯？一个人
Huh? One guy.
一个人！
One guy!
嗯？你这个混蛋！出来！
Huh? You fucker! Come out!
出来！
Come out!
你 对付我 老伙计！
You, deal with me, old man!
硬汉！
Tough guy!
过来 妈的！
Come here, fuck head!
嗯？
Huh?
你要我进去吗？
You want me to come inside?
我会进屋的 我会找到你的
I'll fucking come inside. I'll find you.
等一下
Hold on a second.
你真的很咄咄逼人
You're really aggressive.
你的头发很漂亮
You've got nice hair.
我很佩服你 我真的很佩服你
I admire you, I really do.
你知道 你今晚在这里所做的令人印象深刻
You know, it's impressive what you've done here tonight.
嗯 我还没有完成
Well, I'm not finished yet.
而我才刚刚开始
And I'm only getting started.
你知道 我通常不
As you know, I don't usually
让自己参与任何事情
involve myself personally in anything.
我喜欢操纵事物
I like to manipulate things.
但我真的喜欢这样
But I'm really gonna enjoy this.
我杀人已经很久了
It's been a long time since I killed anyone.
你射杀了一个22岁的男孩
You shot a 22-year-old boy.
这太冷血了 伙计
That's cold-blooded, dude.
是的...我还没有完成
Yeah, well... I'm not done yet.
你是夏威夷人
You Hawaiian man.
他们肯定不再让他们像你一样了
They certainly don't make 'em like you anymore.
你生我的气 因为我帮助了一些有钱的父母
You're pissed at me because I helped some rich parents
摆脱了他们的儿子
get their son off.
我没有杀你的家人
I didn't kill your family.
不管我介入与否 他们都会死的
They'd be dead if I stepped in or not.
那么这一切值得吗？
So is this all worth it?
是的
Yeah.
这是值得的
It's worth it.
也许
Maybe.
我开枪了
I took my shot.
现在 你做你的
Now you take yours.
加油！
Come on!
哦 妈的！
Ow, fuck!
妈的
Shit.
该死
Goddamn.
凯！
Kai!
我应该开枪打你
I should just shoot you.
凯 凯...
Kai, Kai...
是我
It's me.
你他妈的是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
你是出租车司机
You're the cab driver.
她没有参与
She's not involved.
等等 你真的关心她？
Wait, you actually care about her?
她收了贿赂
She took bribe money.
是的 你没有给她选择
Yeah, you didn't give her a choice.
真的 听我说
True. Details.
放开她
Let her go.
你怎么还站着？
How the fuck are you still standing?
请
Please...
放开她
let her go.
我不得不说不
I'm gonna have to say no.
但我会是个好人
But I'm gonna be a nice guy.
我给你一个选择 我先射杀谁？
I'm gonna give you a choice. Who do I shoot first?
对不起
Sorry.
我也是
Me too.
她
Her.
明智的选择
Wise choice.
这个也算我的吗？
Is this on me too?
我对警察感到抱歉
I'm sorry about the cop.
还有护士
And the nurse.
她拥有所有证据 来澄清我家人的名誉
She has all the evidence to clear my family's name.
求你了 做吧
Please, do it.
我把她扣为人质
I held her hostage.
我威胁她哥哥
I threatened her brother.
我强迫她这么做的
I forced her into this.
请叫救护车
Please, call an ambulance.
已经叫了
I already have.
我已经死了
I'm dead.
你知道的
You know that.
我知道 我不值得...
I know I don't deserve it...
但我有个要求
but I have a request.
谢谢
Thank you.